[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest country by area in Africa?", "correct_answer": "Sudan", "incorrect_answers": ["South Africa", "Algeria", "Egypt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What language is adopted as official for the territory of Switzerland?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["German", "Italian", "French"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the occupation of Mary, played by Cameron Diaz, in the 1998 comedy movie Theres Something About Mary?", "correct_answer": "Surgeon", "incorrect_answers": ["Model", "Kindergarten teacher", "Architect"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of the eye is usually referred to as the white of the eye?", "correct_answer": "Sclera", "incorrect_answers": ["Conjunctiva", "All of these", "Stroma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jupiter has rings.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the last name of the main family in My Big Fat Greek Wedding mean?", "correct_answer": "orange", "incorrect_answers": ["pear", "apple", "grape"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the longest river in Poland and the ninth longest in Europe?", "correct_answer": "Vistula", "incorrect_answers": ["Wda", "Nogat", "Dunajec"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the next number in the following sequence, having in mind that it is related to positive integers: 1, 0.5, 0.333, 0.25, 0.2, 0.166, 0.142?", "correct_answer": "0.125", "incorrect_answers": ["0.190", "0.314", "0.100"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Huey Lewis made a cameo appearance in the movie Back to the Future.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the title of this 1993 comedy, directed by Eric Schaffer:  My Lifes...", "correct_answer": "... in Turnaround.", "incorrect_answers": ["... in a Mess.", "... in Arrears.", "...in Couplets."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these regarding the reproduction of raccoons is correct?", "correct_answer": "Pregnancy can last from 54 to 70 days.", "incorrect_answers": ["The male brings food for the young.", "None of these", "Females usually give birth to only one kit."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The family \u201cphocoenidae\u201d describe which group of cetacean?", "correct_answer": "Porpoises", "incorrect_answers": ["Indus and Ganges river dolphins", "Beaked whales", "Dolphins"]}]